m-files.com 2015-09-21

# Privacy Policy Statement | M-Files

### M-Files Privacy Statement

M-Files provides this Privacy Policy to inform our customers, partners and the general public of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information ("PII") received from users of this website, located at www.m-files.com ("Site"). This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

By using our Site you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing" means using cookies on a computer or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information.

PII about you may be processed and stored in the United States or other countries. You hereby consent to the transfer of any PII to the United States or any other country outside of your country of residence where M-Files or its licensees, agents or service providers are providing services or processing or storing PII in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, which countries may provide a different level of data security than in your country of residence. M-Files does not represent or warrant that the Site, or any part thereof, are appropriate or available for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access the Site do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations. We may limit the Site's availability, in whole or in part, to any person, geographic area or jurisdiction we choose, at any time and in our sole discretion.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personally identifiable information, please contact us at [m-files@m-files.com](mailto:m-files.qualitygateway.com?subject=Questions%20Regarding%20M-Files%20Privacy%20Statement).

### Information Collection and Use

The goal of M-Files in collecting PII is to provide you with the product and services made available through the Site, to communicate with you, and, when applicable, to manage your product license and subscription information.

Information Collected Upon Registration. If you wish to download and install M-Files software from the Site, you will be required to register, and to submit certain PII to M-Files. This happens in a number of instances, such as when you register for a trial of our products, or if you wish to receive marketing materials and information. PII that we may collect in such instances may include your IP address, full user name, password, email address, city, time zone, telephone number, and other information that you decide to provide to us.

Use of Contact Information In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about, our products and services. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

Log Information When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This information may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use this information to monitor the use of the Site and for the technical administration of the Site. We do not associate your IP address with any other PII to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Service

### Cookies

Like many websites, we also use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect PII. M-Files may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic on the Site, and to improve the Site and related services. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Service Providers We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your PII with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement M-Files cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of M-Files or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

Business Transfers M-Files may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your PII, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity's planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

### Security

M-Files is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your PII. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

### Links to Other Websites

Our Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

### Safe Harbor

M-Files Safe Harbor Privacy Policy

### Contact

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Site or our Privacy Policy, please contact us.
